Guide to the Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc. Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Organization and Personnel Records/Correspondence, Series II
  - JICUF Individual Files
    - JICUF Individual Files: Women's Planning Committee
      - Peet, Margot - Executive Committee, 1967-1981 (Box 24, Folder 180)
      - Peet, Margot - Executive Committee, 1982-1991 (Box 24, Folder 181)
      - Post, Margaret, 1980-1986 (Box 24, Folder 182)
      - Post, Margaret, 1987-1991 (Box 24, Folder 183)
      - Powers, Kimiko Mae - Executive Committee, 1960-1990 (Box 24, Folder 184)
      - Riggs, Frieda - Executive Committee, 1962-1984 (Box 24, Folder 185)
      - Riggs, Frieda - Executive Committee, 1985-1990 (Box 24, Folder 186)
      - Roeder, Delores - Executive Committee, 1975-1991 (Box 25, Folder 187)
      - Sherman, Opal - Executive Committee, 1963-1975 (Box 25, Folder 188)
      - Sibley, Georgiana - Chairperson, 1953-1988 (Box 25, Folder 189)
      - Sockman, Zellah - Executive Committee, 1963-1981 (Box 25, Folder 190)
      - Tiller, Olive - Executive Committee, 1978-1991 (Box 25, Folder 191)
      - Troyer, Billie, 1967-1978 (Box 25, Folder 192)
      - Troyer, Billie, 1979-1990 (Box 25, Folder 193)
      - Vance, Kazuko - Area Chairperson, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 194)
      - Vining, Elizabeth Gray - Chairperson, 1955-1991 (Box 25, Folder 195)
    - JICUF Individual Files: Local Committees of the Women's Planning Committee
      - Local Committee Handbook (Box 26, Folder 196)
      - Bay Area, Northern California, 1983-1988 (Box 26, Folder 197)
      - Washington D.C.: By-Laws, Constitution, Invitations, 1955-1979 (Box 26, Folder 198)
      - Washington D.C., 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 199)
      - Washington D.C., 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 200)
      - Washington D.C., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 201)
      - Washington D.C., 1976 (Box 26, Folder 202)
      - Washington D.C., 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 203)
      - Washington D.C., 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 204)
      - Washington D.C., 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 205)
      - Washington D.C., 1985-1991 (Box 27, Folder 206)
  - ICU Organization
    - Committee on the Study of ICU's Christian Ideals - final report, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 771)
    - ICU Alumni Association in the Americas - directory, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 772)
  - ICU Individual Files
    - ICU Individual Files: Officers
      - Kamiyama, Setsu - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 207)
      - Kamiyama, Setsu - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 208)
      - Kamiyama, Setsu - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 209)
      - Kamiyama, Setsu - Endowment Trustee, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 210)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President; Visit to the United States, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 211)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 212)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President; Biographical Data, 1958-1976, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 213)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President, 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 214)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 215)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 216)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 217)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 218)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President; Reports to JICUF Board of Directors, 1976-1980 (Box 28, Folder 219)
      - Nakagawa, Hideyasu - President; Reports to JICUF Board of Directors, 1981-1985 (Box 29, Folder 220)
      - Nishida, Kozo - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 221)
      - Nishida, Kozo - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 222)
      - Nishida, Kozo - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 223)
      - Oguchi, Kunio - Dean of College of Liberal Arts, 1967-1984 (Box 29, Folder 224)
      - Oguchi, Kunio - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1986-1991, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 225)
      - Ohara, Haruko - Assistant to the Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 226)
      - Ohara, Haruko - Assistant to the Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1977-1982 (Box 29, Folder 227)
      - Ohara, Haruko - Assistant to the Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 228)
      - Shibanuma, Akira - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 229)
      - Shibanuma, Akira - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 230)
      - Shibanuma, Akira - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 231)
      - Shorrock, Hallam - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1963-1985 (Box 30, Folder 232)
      - Shorrock, Hallam - Special Assistant to the President, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 233)
      - Shorrock, Hallam - Special Assistant to the President, 1987 Jan-Jun (Box 30, Folder 234)
      - Shorrock, Hallam - Special Assistant to the President, 1987 Jul-Dec (Box 30, Folder 235)
      - Shorrock, Hallam - Dean of International Affairs, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 236)
      - Shorrock, Hallam - Dean of International Affairs, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 237)
      - Shorrock, Hallam - Dean of International Affairs, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 238)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 239)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 240)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 241)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 242)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 243)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 244)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 245)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 246)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 247)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 248)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Vice President for Financial Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 249)
      - Tabuchi, Minoru - Endowment Trustee, 1982-1989 (Box 32, Folder 250)
      - Watanabe, Yasuo - President, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 251)
      - Watanabe, Yasuo - President, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 252)
      - Watanabe, Yasuo - President, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 253)
      - Watanabe, Yasuo - President, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 254)
      - Watanabe, Yasuo - President; President's Report to JICUF Board of Directors, 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 255)
      - Watanabe, Yasuo - President; President's Report to JICUF Board of Directors, 1989-1990 (Box 33, Folder 256)
      - Winant, Thomas - Special Assistant to the President, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 257)
    - ICU Individual Files: "Leaders"
      - Cordier, Andrew (See: JICUF Officers)
      - Diffendorfer, Ralph (See: JICUF Officers)
      - Latourette, Kenneth Scott, 1949-1969 (Box 33, Folder 260)
      - MacLean, John, 1946-1949 (Box 33, Folder 261)
      - Rockefeller, Mary, 1958-1963 (Box 33, Folder 262)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1950-1961 (Box 33, Folder 263)
      - Sockman, Ralph, 1959-1973 (Box 33, Folder 264)
      - Sockman Ralph: Record of Gifts, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 265)
      - Chichibu, Setsuko, 1949-1959 (Box 34, Folder 266)
      - Chichibu, Setsuko, 1960-1990 (Box 34, Folder 267)
      - Enomoto, Ryuichiro, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 268)
      - Horinouchi, Kensuke, 1949-1954, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 269)
      - Ichimada, Hisato, 1949-1964, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 270)
      - Kanda, Tateo, 1949-1986 (Box 34, Folder 271)
      - Miyake, Akira, 1963-1970 (Box 34, Folder 272)
      - Miyake, Akira, 1971-1982 (Box 34, Folder 273)
      - Sinoto, Yosito, 1954-1989 (Box 34, Folder 274)
      - Ukai, Nobushige; Yuasa, Hachiro: Inauguration and Investiture Ceremonies, 1949, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 275)
      - Ukai, Nobushige, 1964-1987 (Box 34, Folder 276)
      - Ukai, Nobushige: Speeches, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 277)
      - Yuasa, Hachiro, 1946-1979 (Box 35, Folder 278)
      - Yuasa, Hachiro, 1970-1984 (Box 35, Folder 279)
      - Yuasa, Hachiro: Annual Reports to Board of Directors, JICUF, 1958-1985 (Box 35, Folder 280)
      - Yuasa, Hachiro: Life in Faith, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 281)
      - Yuasa, Hachiro: "Friendship Letters" Presented at Retirement, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 282)
  - Faculty Files
    - Faculty Files: Non-JICUF Sponsored
      - A (Box 35, Folder 283)
      - Akashi, Yasushi, 1969-1972 (Box 35, Folder 284)
      - Arai, Toshitsugu, 1975-1984 (Box 35, Folder 285)
      - C (Box 35, Folder 286)
      - Chikagawa, Sumiko, 1972-1978 (Box 35, Folder 287)
      - E (Box 35, Folder 288)
      - F (Box 35, Folder 289)
      - Fujita, Wakao, 1972-1977 (Box 35, Folder 290)
      - H (Box 35, Folder 291)
      - Harisima, Akira, 1960-1970 (Box 35, Folder 292)
      - I (Box 35, Folder 293)
      - J (Box 35, Folder 294)
      - K (Box 35, Folder 295)
      - Katayama, Waturu, 1971-1975 (Box 36, Folder 296)
      - Kayama, Hisao, 1976-1980, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 297)
      - Kim, Young-jak, 1972-1977 (Box 36, Folder 298)
      - L (Box 36, Folder 299)
      - M (Box 36, Folder 300)
      - Macrory, Patrick Francis John, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 301)
      - N (Box 36, Folder 302)
      - O (Box 36, Folder 303)
      - Ogata, Sadako, 1974-1991 (Box 36, Folder 304)
      - Owaku, Yasutaro, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 305)
      - P (Box 36, Folder 306)
      - Q (Box 36, Folder 307)
      - R (Box 36, Folder 308)
      - S (Box 36, Folder 309)
      - T (Box 36, Folder 310)
      - Takahashi, Tane, 1954-1982 (Box 36, Folder 311)
      - W (Box 36, Folder 312)
      - X, Y, Z (Box 36, Folder 313)
      - Yamamoto, Tatsuro, 1971-1976 (Box 36, Folder 314)
      - Yamashita, Yoshichika, 1969-1976 (Box 36, Folder 315)
    - Faculty Files: JICUF Sponsored
      - B (Box 36, Folder 316)
      - Boulding, Kenneth, 1961-1982 (Box 37, Folder 317)
      - Brown, Holloway: Financial Information, 1968-1987 (Box 37, Folder 318)
      - Brown, Holloway, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 319-325)
      - Brown, Holloway, 1978-1989 (Box 38, Folder 326-334)
      - C (Box 39, Folder 335)
      - Condon, John C. Jr., 1969-1980 (Box 39, Folder 336)
      - Cubbage, Moyne L., 1961-1967 (Box 39, Folder 337)
      - D (Box 39, Folder 338)
      - E (Box 39, Folder 339)
      - F (Box 39, Folder 340)
      - G (Box 39, Folder 341)
      - Gerhard, Robert H, 1952-1989 (Box 39, Folder 342)
      - Gold, Alan J., 1982-1985 (Box 39, Folder 343)
      - H (Box 39, Folder 344)
      - Harder, Bernhard, 1978-1982 (Box 39, Folder 345)
      - Hartmann, Walter, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 346)
      - Holvik, Leonard C., 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 347)
      - Horowitz, David, 1986-1991 (Box 39, Folder 348)
      - K (Box 39, Folder 349)
      - Kleinjans, Everett, 1962-1990 (Box 40, Folder 350)
      - Kleinjans, Everett: Reports to JICUF, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 351)
      - Kleinjans, Everett: Reports to JICUF, 1965-1967 (Box 40, Folder 352)
      - L (Box 40, Folder 353)
      - Leong, Sow-Theng, 1967-1971 (Box 40, Folder 354)
      - Leuenberger, Theodor, 1966-1972 (Box 40, Folder 355)
      - Lindstrom, David E., 1953, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 356)
      - M (Box 40, Folder 357)
      - MacDonald, Mary Lee, 1952-1982 (Box 40, Folder 358)
      - Mc (Box 40, Folder 359)
      - Miller, Richard J., 1964-1978 (Box 40, Folder 360)
      - Mitchell, Sidney, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 361a)
      - Moore, William, 1954-1975 (Box 40, Folder 361b)
      - Morsbach, Helmut P., 1966-1972 (Box 41, Folder 362)
      - Munsterberg, Hugo, 1952-1989 (Box 41, Folder 363)
      - N (Box 41, Folder 364)
      - O (Box 41, Folder 365)
      - Owada, Yasuyuki, 1969-1987 (Box 41, Folder 366)
      - R (Box 41, Folder 367)
      - Ramsey, Sheila J., 1977-1991 (Box 41, Folder 368)
      - Rich, Elaine Sommers, 1966-1981 (Box 41, Folder 369)
      - Rich, Ronald L., 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 370)
      - Rich, Ronald L., 1971-1977 (Box 41, Folder 371)
      - Rich, Ronald L., 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 372)
      - S (Box 42, Folder 373)
      - Saito, Kazuaki, 1980-1990 (Box 42, Folder 374)
      - T (Box 42, Folder 375)
      - Tong, Curtis W., 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 376)
      - Troyer, Maurice E., 1955-1964 (Box 42, Folder 377)
      - Troyer, Maurice E., 1967-1987 (Box 42, Folder 378)
      - Troyer, Maurice E. - JICUF Board Member, 1974-1991 (Box 42, Folder 379)
      - U (Box 42, Folder 380)
      - V (Box 42, Folder 381)
      - W (Box 42, Folder 382)
      - Worth, Donald - Biographical Data, 1949-1981, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 383)
      - Worth, Donald - Financial Data, 1968-1990 (Box 42, Folder 384)
      - Worth, Donald, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 385)
      - Worth, Donald, 1970-1976 (Box 43, Folder 386)
      - Worth, Donald, 1977-1980 (Box 43, Folder 387)
      - Worth, Donald, 1981-1991 (Box 43, Folder 388)
      - X, Y, Z (Box 43, Folder 389)
      - Yee, Herbert Sun-Jun, 1980-1983 (Box 43, Folder 390)
      - Princeton-In-Asia Fellows (Box 43, Folder 391)
- Events, Programs, Series III
  JICUF/ICU Meetings
  Fundraisers/ Benefits
  Anniversaries
  NY Office Closing Ceremonies
  Men's Committee Events
  Women's Planning Committee Events
  Programs
  - JICUF/ICU Meetings
    - Second Decade Conference, 1963 Nov (Box 44, Folder 392)
    - Foundation Deputation to ICU, 1965-1966 (Box 44, Folder 393)
    - Hachiro Yuasa's Visit to New York, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 394)
    - "Report on Visit to ICU" - by Betty Gray, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 395)
    - Consultation Meeting In Japan - Betty Gray's Notes and Schedule, 1987 Apr (Box 44, Folder 396)
    - Consultation Meeting in Japan, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 397)
    - Consultation Meeting in Japan - Financial, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 398)
    - Consultation Meeting in Japan - Planning, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 399)
    - Consultation Meeting in Japan - Summary of Discussions, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 400)
    - Consultation in New York, 1987 Jun (Box 44, Folder 401)
    - Discussions in New York - Reservations and Planning, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 402)
    - Discussions in New York - Agenda, Proposals, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 403)
    - Discussions in New York - Memo to Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 404)
    - Discussions in New York - Alumni Dinner, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 405)
  - Fundraisers/Benefits
    - Cherry Tree Planting Services - Colleges, 1964-1966, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 406)
    - Cherry Tree Planting Services - Churches, 1964-1966, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 407)
    - Cherry Tree Planting Services - Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1962-1971 (Box 45, Folder 408)
    - JICUF Family Dinner, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 409)
    - Fashion Show "Elegance and Energy", 1985 (Box 45, Folder 410)
    - Hawaii Benefits, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 411)
  - Anniversaries
    - Tenth Anniversary
      - "ICU, The First Ten Years, 1949-1959" (Box 45, Folder 412)
      - "ICU Tenth Anniversary Bulletin", 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 413)
      - Dinner - October 15, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 414)
      - Dinner - October 15, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 415)
      - "The Importance of ICU" - by John D. Rockefeller, IV (See Also Series Ii Files: Men's Committee, Rockefeller), 1963 (Box 45, Folder 416)
      - "ICU - A Christian's Hope for the Future" - by Nobushige Ukai, 1963 Oct (Box 45, Folder 417)
      - Affairs in Governors' Mansions, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 418)
      - Governors' Mansions: Colorado - Iowa, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 419)
      - Governors' Mansions: Maryland - Vermont, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 420)
      - Governors' Mansions: Washington - Wyoming, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 421)
      - Congratulatory Letters - College Presidents, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 422)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Members of Cabinet, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 423)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Methodist Bishops, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 424)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Evangelical Brethren Bishops, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 425)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Governors, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 426)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Senators, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 427)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 428)
      - 20th Program Photos (Box 46, Folder 429)
    - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary
      - Leaflets, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 430)
      - Logo/Emblem, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 431)
      - Appeal Letter, 1974 Feb (Box 46, Folder 432)
      - 25th Anniversary Conference, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 433)
      - Congratulatory Letters, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 434)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Church Leaders, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 435)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Foundation, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 436)
      - Congratulatory Letters - Women's Denominational Organizations, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 437)
      - "Alumni Evaluation of Their ICU Experience", 1975 (Box 47, Folder 438)
      - Honorary Degrees, Celebration Program, 1973, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 439)
      - Photo Contest, 1974, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 440)
      - Articles, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 441)
      - Articles Received, 1974, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 442)
      - Newspaper Releases, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 443)
      - Publicity Received, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 444)
      - Endorsements for ICU, 1973, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 445)
      - Worship Services, 1973, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 446)
      - Congratulatory Letters, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 447)
      - Congratulatory Letters, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 448)
      - Miscellaneous Material, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 449)
      - Local Observances, Suggested Conveners, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 450)
      - Local Observances, Suggested Chairwomen, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 451)
      - Alabama, Prattville, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 452)
      - Arkansas, Little Rock, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 453)
      - Colorado, Denver, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 454)
      - Connecticut, Ridgefield, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 455)
      - Connecticut, Southbury, 1974, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 456)
      - Delaware, Dover, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 457)
      - Florida, Hollywood, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 458)
      - Florida, Jacksonville, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 459)
      - Florida, Tallahasee, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 460)
      - Florida, Weirsdale, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 461)
      - Georgia, Atlanta, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 462)
      - Illinois, Chicago, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 463)
      - Illinois, Evanston, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 464)
      - Illinois, Oak Brook, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 465)
      - Maryland, Baltimore, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 466)
      - Maryland, Gaithersburg, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 467)
      - Massachusetts, Wellesley, 1973-1976 (Box 48, Folder 468)
      - Minnesota, St. Paul - Minneapolis, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 469)
      - New Hampshire, Lisbon, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 470)
      - New Jersey, Highland Park, 1973, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 471)
      - New Jersey, Montclair, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 472)
      - New Jersey, Ocean City, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 473)
      - New York, Albany, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 474)
      - New York, Brooklyn, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 475)
      - New York, Buffalo Area, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 476)
      - New York, Mount Vernon, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 477)
      - New York, Poughkeepsie, 1973-1976 (Box 49, Folder 478)
      - New York, Scarsdale, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 479)
      - New York, Syracuse, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 480)
      - North Carolina, Shelby, 1973, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 481)
      - Ohio, Cleveland, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 482)
      - Ohio, Athens, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 483)
      - Ohio, Sylvania, 1974, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 484)
      - Ohio, Wooster, 1974, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 485)
      - Oklahoma, Enid, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 486)
      - Oklahoma, Tulsa, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 487)
      - Oregon, McMinnville, 1973, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 488)
      - Pennsylvania, Glenshaw, 1973, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 489)
      - Pennsylvania, Harrisburg, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 490)
      - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 491)
      - Pennsylvania, Williamsport, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 492)
      - South Carolina, Columbia, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 493)
      - South Carolina, Hartsville, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 494)
      - Tennessee, Nashville, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 495)
      - Texas, Lavedo, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 496)
      - Utah, Murray, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 497)
      - Virginia, Richmond, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 498)
      - Washington, Seattle, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 499)
      - West Virginia, Huntington, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 500)
      - West Virginia, Morgantown, 1973, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 501)
    - 30th- 40th Anniversaries
      - 30th Anniversary - Articles Printed, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 502)
      - 30th Anniversary - Suggested Special Activities (Box 49, Folder 503)
      - 35th Anniversary - University Chapel, 1984 Jun (Box 49, Folder 504)
      - 35th Anniversary - Interchurch Center Exhibit, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 505)
      - 35th Anniversary - Interchurch Center Exhibit, Opening Reception, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 506)
      - 40th Anniversary - Berkeley, California, 1989 Jun (Box 49, Folder 507)
      - 40th Anniversary - Recognition Banquet, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 508)
  - NY Office Closing Ceremonies
    - Fall Luncheon, 1991 Oct (Box 50, Folder 509)
    - Fall Luncheon - Thank You Notes, 1991 Oct (Box 50, Folder 510)
    - Fall Luncheon - Photographs, 1991 Oct (Box 50, Folder 511)
  - Men's Committee Events
    - Luncheon, 1965 Jan (Box 50, Folder 512)
    - Meeting, 1965 Mar (Box 50, Folder 513)
    - Luncheon, 1968 Jun (Box 50, Folder 514)
    - Luncheon, 1970 May (Box 50, Folder 515)
    - Luncheon, 1975 Nov (Box 50, Folder 516)
  - Women's Planning Committee Events
    - Tea Honoring Hachiro Yuasa, 1961 Sep (Box 50, Folder 517)
    - Special Project: Health and Physical Education, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 518)
    - Luncheon Meeting of Executive Committee, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 519)
    - Annual Meeting, 1963 Jan (Box 50, Folder 520)
    - Executive Board Meeting, 1966 May (Box 50, Folder 521)
    - Luncheon Meeting, 1966 Jun (Box 50, Folder 522)
    - Annual Meeting, 1968 Jan (Box 50, Folder 523)
    - Luncheon Meeting, 1968 Jun (Box 50, Folder 524)
    - Annual Meeting, 1969 Jan (Box 50, Folder 525)
    - Luncheon Meeting, 1969 Jun (Box 50, Folder 526)
    - Annual Meeting, 1976 Jun (Box 50, Folder 527)
    - Tree Planting, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1977 Mar (Box 50, Folder 528)
    - Luncheon with Reiko, Kitadai, 1986 Apr (Box 50, Folder 529)
    - Benefit Art Exhibit and Luncheon, 1991 Jan (Box 51, Folder 530)
    - First Annual Luncheon (with Eleanor Roosevelt), 1953 Nov (Box 51, Folder 531)
    - Second Annual Luncheon, 1955 Jan (Box 51, Folder 532)
    - Third Annual Luncheon, 1956 Nov (Box 51, Folder 533)
    - Fourth Annual Luncheon, 1957 Oct (Box 51, Folder 534)
    - Fifth Annual Luncheon, 1958 Oct (Box 51, Folder 535)
    - Sixth Annual Luncheon, 1960 Oct (Box 51, Folder 536)
    - Seventh Annual Luncheon, 1962 Oct (Box 51, Folder 537)
    - Eighth Annual Luncheon, 1964 Oct (Box 51, Folder 538)
    - Ninth Annual Luncheon, 1965 Oct (Box 51, Folder 539)
    - Tenth Annual Luncheon, 1966 Oct (Box 51, Folder 540)
    - Eleventh Annual Luncheon, 1967 Oct (Box 51, Folder 541)
    - Twelfth Annual Luncheon, 1969 Oct (Box 52, Folder 542)
    - Thirteenth Annual Luncheon, 1970 Oct (Box 52, Folder 543)
    - Fourteenth Annual Luncheon, 1971 Oct (Box 52, Folder 544)
    - Fifteenth Anniversary Luncheon, 1968 Oct (Box 52, Folder 545)
    - Twentieth Anniversary Luncheon, 1973 May (Box 52, Folder 546)
    - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Luncheon, 1974 Oct (Box 52, Folder 547)
    - Thirtieth Anniversary Luncheon, 1979 Nov (Box 52, Folder 548)
  - Programs